inst.ag 2013-07-31

# Inst.ag Privacy Policy 2012-06-26.docx

Pokki Privacy Policy

SweetLabs, Inc. (“We” or “SweetLabs”) know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This Pokki Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other information We gather when you are accessing our Pokki-related website(s) (the “Pokki Site” or “Pokki Sites”).  Such Pokki Sites include [http://www.pokki.com](http://www.pokki.com/), [http://www.tweeki.com](http://www.tweeki.com/), <http://inst.ag/>, and our store (the “Pokki App Store”), a publicly available app marketplace located at www.pokki.com (or such other site operated by SweetLabs), and/or integrated with the Pokki desktop client 

In addition, this Pokki Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of Personal Information and other information We gather when you use any of our Pokki-related services or products, including downloading or using a web-connected desktop application utilizing the Pokki platform (a “Pokki App” or “Pokki Apps”) or by using any other services or products on or through a Pokki Site or through a Pokki App.

By visiting our Pokki Sites, using a Pokki App, or using any of our Pokki-related services or products, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Pokki Privacy Policy.

Please note this policy does not apply to (and We are not responsible for) the practices of companies that We do not own or control or to individuals We do not employ or manage. When utilizing third party sites or software products, including Pokki Apps that may be provided by third parties or Pokki Apps or Pokki Sites that access or utilize third party sites or services, you should read the relevant privacy policies of those third parties for information regarding their privacy practices.

  1. SUMMARY OF OUR POKKI PRIVACY POLICY

SweetLabs maintains or provides multiple Pokki-related sites, products and services.  To better explain what information We collect, and how We use the information We collect, We have broken out our Pokki Privacy Policy into the following sections:  

        Section 2:  WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY.  This section explains what information We collect from: 

(a) users who install Pokki App(s);

(b) Pokki App developers and publishers; and 

(c) visitors to our Pokki Sites, including the Pokki App Store.

        Section 3:  HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED.  This section explains how We use your information, and why, as well as if and how We share your information.  

        Sections 4-8:  These sections discuss various topics, including how We protect any information We collect, how you can update any information you share with us, our compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, our storage and use of information from users outside the United States, and how We may alert you of any changes to this Pokki Privacy Policy.    

  2. WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY

  1. USERS WHO INSTALL Pokki AppS. 

If you are a user who has installed a Pokki App, We collect the following types of information:

Usage Information. Generally, our Pokki platform software automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency with which a Pokki App has been clicked or opened, and how long a Pokki App remains open.  In addition, Pokki Apps that We have developed may include in-app analytics that collect information such as the features used and the number and frequency of clicks that occur within such Pokki App. We also collect installation information, which may include information on whether a Pokki App has been installed or uninstalled, or your geo-location, operating system and language setting.  Any information We collect is not personally identifiable, and We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally, to allow us to improve the Pokki platform.

Users with Accounts.  If you have created a user account, we collect and maintain all information that you provide to us in connection with the creation of your Pokki user account, including Personal Information such as your name, email address, date of birth and photo (if you have chosen to upload a photo to your user account profile). The Personal Information you provide in connection with your account is used in order to help us manage your account and provide services and features in connection with your account. 

Third Party Pokki Apps and Sites.  If you have installed a Pokki App provided by a third party, or a Pokki App that accesses third party sites or services, then that third party may also collect information regarding your usage of such Pokki App, or your access or usage of the third party sites or services accessed by such Pokki App.  Any information collected by a third party provider of a Pokki App, or a site or service accessed by a Pokki App, is governed by such third party providers’ privacy policies.  These third party sites may also place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you.  We do not exercise control over any third party sites that a Pokki App or other third party application, may link to.

  2. Pokki App Developers & Publishers  

If you are a software developer or publisher that uses the Pokki.com site to publish or distribute your Pokki App, We also collect the following types of information:

Account Information. We collect and maintain all information that you provide to us in connection with the Pokki App submission, review and approval process in order to help us manage your account and communicate with you regarding our review of a submitted Pokki App.

  3. Website Visitors  

If you are a visitor to our Pokki Sites, including the Pokki App Store, We collect the following types of information:

Cookies. When you visit our Pokki Sites, We will send you a cookie which is stored on your computer and allows us to uniquely identify it. We use cookies to help us better understand our users  which allows us to improve our products and services. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which helps us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively. 

Logs. When you visit our Pokki Sites, We capture and store the data that your computer sends us. This data may include your browser type, language, Internet Protocol address, the date and time of your request and the cookie that helps us identify your computer.

Usage Information. Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Pokki Sites and its components, including usage information regarding the Pokki App Store. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of our Pokki Sites, products or services so that We can improve the performance of our products and services.

Communication.  Anytime you send us a communication We may keep this communication so that We can respond to your requests or inquiries and help improve our services to you.  Posts to our Support pages located within support.pokki.com will display your user name as you have indicated it in your profile.

Information You Provide.  We also receive and store any information you enter on our Pokki Sites, including the Pokki App Store, or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, user name and email address. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as improving the content of our sites, customizing and improving our services, and communicating with you about specials and new features.  

Third Party Applications.  We may make available third party applications or services through the Pokki Sites and the Pokki App Store, including third party Pokki Apps or Pokki Apps that access third party sites or services. The information collected by us when you enable or use a third party application, including a third party Pokki App, is processed under this Pokki Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party provider of a Pokki App, or the third party provider of a site or service accessed by a Pokki App, is governed by such third party providers’ privacy policies.

Other Sites. This Pokki Privacy Policy only applies to the Pokki Sites, and the Pokki App Store. We do not exercise control over any third party sites that a Pokki Site, or that a Pokki App or other third party application, may link to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you.

* * *

3.     HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED

  1. For Pokki App Users Without a User Account.  

Any information we collect is not personally identifiable, and we only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally, to allow us to improve the Pokki platform.  We do not sell or otherwise market this information to third parties.  

For Pokki App Users With a User Account.  

If you have created a user account and have posted information on a leaderboard or reviewed a Pokki App, your first name and photo (if you have chosen to upload a photo to your user account profile) will be displayed with your review or leaderboard information on the Pokki Site or within the pertinent Pokki App.  If you have created a user account and have shared a Pokki App with another user, your first name and photo (if one has been uploaded to your user account profile) will be shared with users with which you have chosen to share a Pokki App.

  2. For Pokki App Developers and Publishers.  

We may share your Personal Information with third party agents for the purpose of approving and enabling your participation in the Pokki App Store. For example, processing and approving your Pokki App submissions, email, analyzing data, and providing other partner services. Unless We tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use Personal Information We share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

  3. For all Personal Information and other Information We Collect.  We may also share or use your Personal Information or other information as follows:  

  1. Protection of SweetLabs and Others. We may share your Personal Information and other information if We have a good faith belief that it is required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Pokki Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and SweetLabs, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of SweetLabs, its visitors, users and/or the public.
  2. Business Transfers. If SweetLabs or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that SweetLabs goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that would be transferred to, or acquired by, a third party acquiror. Accordingly, We may transfer or assign all the information We have collected as part of a merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror may continue to use your Personal Information and other information as set forth in this policy.
  3. Non-Personal Information. We may share your non-personally identifiable information with partners and other third parties for the purpose of helping us improve the Pokki platform and the overall performance of our products and services, or allow us to provide recommendations. For example, utilizing data to determine the probability that a consumer will enjoy a specific Pokki App or product.
  4. With Your Consent. Except as set forth above, We will only share your Personal Information with third parties with your prior consent.

 4.     INFORMATION SECURITY

We endeavor to take security measures to guard against unauthorized access to the systems where We store your data. This includes internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures and physical security measures. However, despite the measures We take We cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

5\.          UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

Through the process provided on our site, We allow you to access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. The types of information that you can access and update will change as our site changes. You may request deletion of your account by sending an e-mail developer account deletion at [privacy@pokki.com](mailto:privacy@pokki.com) and responding affirmatively to any confirmation e-mails that We may send. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

6\.          Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), We will not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.  We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the websites that their children visit.  The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which website operators collect and use Personal Information from children under 13, pursuant to COPPA.  For more information about COPPA and children's on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC's website at www.ftc.gov/privacy.  For safety tips on privacy visit [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/).

7.     USERS LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

Our Pokki Sites, Pokki Apps, and other services and products are hosted by servers located in the United States.  If you are located outside the United States, your information will be transferred to our servers in the United States.  By visiting our Pokki Sites, or using a Pokki App or any of our services or products, you consent to the transfer, storage and use of your information in the United States.  

8.        POLICY CHANGES

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. If We make changes in the way We use Personal Information, We will notify you by posting an announcement on Pokki.com or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Pokki Privacy Policy when he or she uses our site or services after such changes have been first posted.

If you have feedback, questions or concerns contact us at Privacy, c/o SweetLabs, Inc., 510 Market St, Ste 301, San Diego, CA 92101 or email us at privacy@pokki.com.

Effective Date of this Pokki Privacy Policy:  July 9, 2012
